Contact

Pune, MH, 411030

880 648 3999

shwetawadnere3@gmail.

https://www.linkedin.co m/in/shweta-wadnere-82 a5221

Skills

Public Speaking

Excellent

Relationship building



Leadership



Negotiation



MS Office



Languages

English



Hindi



Marathi





Shweta Wadnere

Enthusiastic and adaptable to changing needs and polished in multitasking to handle fast-paced sales, administrative and marketing needs. Experienced t in rendering support to sales representative, developing various marketing campaigns and generating lead lists.. Hardworking and communicative individual possessing magnificent research and presentation skills.

Work History

2020-04 -

2018-08 -

2018-12

Sales and Marketing Intern

Zeallyons Organization, Pune, Maharashtra

- Demonstrated products to customers, answered questions and redirected objectives to positive features.
- Tried to find and implement new sales opportunities each week and leveraged knowledge of company goals and strategies to offer insight into viability of potential connections.
- Supported sales team with administrative assistance such as coordinating paperwork and responding to basic inquiries.
- Tracked, measured and reported on trends for sales team analysis and decision making.
- Initiated contact with prospects and conducted follow-up calls to garner information and qualify leads.
- Cold called perspective customers to determine product or service needs, ascertain timelines, and identify decision-makers.

Career Counselor

Reliance Education (Big Animation (I) Pvt. Ltd.). Pune, Maharashtra

- Cold called perspective customers to determine product or service needs, ascertain timelines, and identify decision-makers.
- Initiated contact with prospects and conducted follow-up calls to garner information and qualify leads.
- Established and oversaw clear guidelines about procedures and success metrics.
- Worked with team to continuously improve career and placement opportunities for students.
- Maintained knowledge of market and diverse career opportunities.

Education

2019-06 - MBA: Business Administration
2021-06 - MITWPU - Pune
2015-06 - BBA: Business Administration
2018-04 - M.E.S Garware College Of Commerce - Pune

Certifications

2020-04 Fundamentals of Digital Marketing - Google Digital Unlocked

2021-04 Social Media Marketing- eMarketing Institute

2020-04 Email Marketing- eMarketing Institute

2017-08 Soft Skill Development Program

Additional Information

- · Participated and volunteered in E- Cell / ED Cell.
- Participated in various activities such as Mad Ads and Business Fairs.
- Active participation in various dance competitions and won the prizes for the same.
- Learnt Classical dance(Kathak) and Classical music.

Interests/ Hobbies

Dance

Travelling and Exploring New Places

Singing